<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="#F1F6F9"
    tools:context=".AboutActivity">

    <androidx.appcompat.widget.Toolbar
        android:id="@+id/toolbar"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="?attr/actionBarSize"
        android:background="#F1F6F9"
        android:elevation="3dp">
        <Button
            android:id="@+id/btn_back"
            android:background="@null"
            android:drawableStart="@drawable/ic_back"
            android:drawableTint="@color/black"
            android:layout_width="48dp"
            android:layout_height="?attr/actionBarSize"
            android:contentDescription="back button"/>
        <TextView
            android:fontFamily="@font/geologica_regular"
            android:text="About"
            android:textSize="18sp"
            android:layout_gravity="center"
            android:gravity="center"
            android:textColor="@color/black"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"/>
    </androidx.appcompat.widget.Toolbar>

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_below="@+id/toolbar"
        android:orientation="vertical"
        android:padding="16dp"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content">
        <ImageView
            android:src="@drawable/logo_mathuto_black"
            android:layout_width="130dp"
            android:layout_height="50dp"/>
        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/tv_about"
            android:text="This capstone project focuses on developing and evaluating Mathuto Math, a mobile learning application designed to enhance mathematics education for grade 6 students. The project aims to investigate the application's impact on students' mathematical skills, concepts, problem-solving abilities, and overall performance. The goal is to contribute to the field of education by providing a tailored mobile learning solution for grade 6 mathematics. The evaluation of Mathuto Math's effectiveness will provide valuable insights for educators and serve as a foundation for future enhancements in math education mobile applications, Mathuto Math utilizes a Sorting algorithm to randomize quiz questions, offering a unique experience with each playthrough. The application includes quizzes, instructions, lessons, and a scoring display, all presented in an engaging and interactive manner. This approach caters to students who may face challenges with traditional mathematics teaching methods. The study involved gathering data from respondents, including satisfactory ratings and assessments based on ISO 9126 standards, which evaluate the application's quality for both mathematics teachers and IT professionals. Pre-test and post-test assessments were conducted, along with an examination of six key quality characteristics. The results showed a rating of 5.12 for the six elements, indicating strong agreement on the Likert scale. The students' evaluation yielded a mean average of 5.12, indicating agreement. Based on the findings, the developers concluded that Mathuto Math effectively improved students' performance after engaging with the application."
            android:fontFamily="@font/geologica_regular"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"/>
    </LinearLayout>

</RelativeLayout>